Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Media Relations Records
- Men's Basketball, 1911-2008; 1911 2008; The first official Men's Basketball game was played in 1911 against Wake Forest, and was held in the old Pullen Hall auditorium. In 1924, home games were moved from Raleigh Memorial Auditorium to the first on-campus facility: Thompson Gymnasium. With a 13-6 
  - Statistics, box scores, 1965-1966 (Legalbox 24, Folder 1)
  - Varsity Basketball clippings, 1965-1966 (Legalbox 24, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 14 Dec. 1965 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Triangle Double-Headers program, 30-31 Dec. 1965 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 10 Feb. 1966 (Box 266, Folder 37)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament box scores, 3-5 Mar. 1966 (Legalbox 24, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament program, 3-5 Mar. 1966 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Tournament: East Regional box scores, 11-12 Mar. 1966 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Regional program, 11-12 Mar. 1966 (Box 266, Folder 38)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1966-1967 (Legalbox 24, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Basketball score book, 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Programs (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Programs (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, box scores (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Legalbox 24, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, box scores (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Legalbox 24, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Basketball clippings, 1966-1967 (Legalbox 24, Folder 7)
  - Varsity Basketball score book, 1966-1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Triangle Classic: clippings, 30-31 Dec. 1966 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 7 Jan. 1967 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - North-South Double Header: clippings, 17-18 Feb. 1967 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: clippings, 9-11 Mar. 1967 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1967-1968 (Legalbox 24, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Basketball score book, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Media guide, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Programs (1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Programs (2 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Programs (3 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, box scores (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Legalbox 24, Folder 9)
  - Statistics, box scores (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Legalbox 25, Folder 1)
  - Varsity Basketball clippings, 1967-1968 (Legalbox 25, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament program, 7-9 Mar. 1968 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional, 15-16 Mar. 1968 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Brochure, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Basketball general information, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Programs (1 of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Programs (2 of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Season ticket form, 1968-1969 (Box 264, Folder 66)
  - Statistics, 1968-1969 (Legalbox 25, Folder 3)
  - Varsity Basketball statistics, 1968-1969 (Legalbox 25, Folder 4)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament program, 6-8 Mar. 1969 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional program, 13-15 Mar. 1969 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Box scores (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Box scores (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 264, Folder 67)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 264, Folder 68)
  - Freshman Basketball general information, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Media guide, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Play-by-play scoring, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Schedule, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest: clippings, 1970 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional, 12, 14 Mar. 1970 (Legalbox 102, Folder 7)
  - Box scores, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Freshman Basketball general information, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Basketball statistics, 1970-1971 (Legalbox 25, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Score books, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1970-1971 (Legalbox 102, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional handbook, 18-20 Mar. 1971 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Box scores, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Coder/Huets investigation, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Basketball questionnaires, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Basketball score book, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Score book, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1971-1972 (Flatbox 272)
  - Statistics, box scores (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Legalbox 102, Folder 9)
  - Statistics, box scores (2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Legalbox 102, Folder 10)
  - Varsity Basketball questionnaires, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Basketball School for Boys (16th Annual), Jun. - Aug. 1972 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Box scores, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Clippings (1 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (2 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (3 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (4 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (5 of 5), 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Basketball clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Ken-L-Ration Award, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Media guide, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Pre-season clippings, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Pre-season information requests, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Press permit, 1972-1973 (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Programs (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Programs (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Score books, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 3), 1972-1973 (Flatbox 267)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 3), 1972-1973 (Flatbox 268)
  - Scrapbook (3 of 3), 1972-1973 (Flatbox 269)
  - Statistics, box scores (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Legalbox 103, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, box scores (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Legalbox 103, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament clippings, 8-10 Mar. 1973 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Media guide (2 copies), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - North-South Double-Header, 1973-1979 (Legalbox 25, Folder 9)
  - Photo press pass, 1973-1974 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Score book, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook (3 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook (4 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (5 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (6 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook (7 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook (8 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (9 of 9), 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - "State Wins NCAA Championship" poster, 1973-1974 (Flatfolder 18)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1973-1974 (Legalbox 25, Folder 8)
  - Team photograph and signatures (reproductions), 1973-1974 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Varsity Basketball score book, Feb. - Mar. 1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs.Pepperdine, Louisville, Texas A&M (Alaska Shootout), 26-27 Nov. 1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke: program, 4 Feb. 1974 (Box 266, Folder 39)
  - NCAA Tournament: Eastern Regional, 14-16 Mar. 1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Japan trip, Aug. 1974 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook: Trip to Philippines, games against Philippines National Basketball Team, 10-13 Aug. 1974 (Flatbox 270)
  - Junior Varsity Basketball general information, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Media guide, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Schedule poster, 1974-1975 (Flatfolder 4)
  - Score book, 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Score book, Mar. 1975 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook (3 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook (4 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (5 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (6 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook (7 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook (8 of 8), 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook (created by fan), 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1974-1975 (Legalbox 25, Folder 10)
  - Expo '74, Sept. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Red-White game, 9 Nov. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Athletes in Action, 28 Nov. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina University, 30 Nov. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Asheville, 3 Dec. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Buffalo State, 5 Dec. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 7 Dec. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Oregon State, 14 Dec. 1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Davidson, 21 Dec. 1974 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Kent State, Pittsburgh (Holiday Double Header), 27-28 Dec. 1974 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Kent State (Holiday Classic), 27 Dec. 1974 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Pittsburgh (Holiday Classic), 28 Dec. 1974 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Big Four Tournament general information, 3-4 Jan. 1975 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest (Big Four Tournament), 3 Jan. 1975 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (Big Four Tournament), 4 Jan. 1975 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina, 9 Jan. 1975 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 16 Jan. 1975 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 18 Jan. 1975 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 25 Jan. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 27 Jan. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 1 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 4 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - North-South Double Header: general information, 7-8 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech (North-South Double Header), 7 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Furman (North-South Double Header), 8 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 12 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 15 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 19 Feb. 1975 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 22 Feb. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 25 Feb. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte, 1 Mar. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament: general information, Mar. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia (Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament), 6 Mar. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Maryland (Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament), 7 Mar. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament), 8 Mar. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Tournament: First Round, Eastern Regional, 15 Mar. 1975 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Box Scores, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - General information, clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Media guide, 1975-1976 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Programs (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Programs (2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Programs (3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Score book, Nov. 1975 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Score book, 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1975-1976 (Legalbox 25, Folder 11)
  - Denver Nuggets vs. New Orleans Jazz (at Reynolds Coliseum), 1975 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Red-White game, 1 Nov. 1975 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Athletes in Action, 15 Nov. 1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. The Citadel, 29 Nov. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina, 3 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Asheville, 6 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina, 13 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Michigan State, 20 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Western Kentucky, Auburn (Holiday Double Header), 26-27 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Western Kentucky (Holiday Double Header), 26 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Auburn (Holiday Double Header), 27 Dec. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Big Four Tournament, 2-3 Jan. 1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian State, 7 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Rollins, 10 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 14 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 16 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 18 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 24 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 28 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 31 Jan. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 3 Feb. 1976 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - North-South Double Header program, 6-7 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Furman, 6 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech, 7 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte, 11 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 14 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 18 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 21 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 24 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 28 Feb. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament, 4-6 Mar. 1976 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - National Invitation Tournament, Mar. 1976 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - National Invitation Tournament media guide, Mar. 1976 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Box scores, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Brochure materials, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Clippings: general information, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Clippings: Player of the Week, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - General information, 1976-1983 (Legalbox 26, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Programs (1 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Programs (2 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Programs (3 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Recruiting for 1977-1978 season, 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Score book, 1976-1977 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Score book, Mar. 1977 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1976-1977 (Legalbox 25, Folder 12)
  - Red-White game, 1 Nov. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Windsor University, 13 Nov. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (Big Four Tournament), 26 Nov. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Big Four Tournament general information, 27 Nov. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 4 Dec. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian, 8 Dec. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. University of Nevada-Reno, 11 Dec. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Michigan State, 20 Dec. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Oregon State, 22 Dec. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Rice, Duke vs. East Carolina (Duke Double Header), 29 Dec. 1976 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina, Duke vs. Rice (Duke Double Header), 30 Dec. 1976 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. North Carolina A & T, 3 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Western Carolina, 6 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 9 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 15 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 19 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 22 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 27 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 29 Jan. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 1 Feb. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Furman (North-South Double Header), 4 Feb. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Tech (North-South Double Header), 5 Feb. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Davidson, 9 Feb. 1977 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 12 Feb. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 16 Feb. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 19 Feb. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 23 Feb. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 26 Feb. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament general information, 3-5 Mar. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament program, 3-5 Mar. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland (Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament), 3 Mar. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament), 4 Mar. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - NCAA Tournament, Mar. 1977 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Box scores (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Box scores (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Legalbox 26, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: All-Conference, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - General information (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - General information (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Media guide, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Photograps: coaching staff, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Score books, 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1977-1978 (Legalbox 26, Folder 3)
  - Red-White game, 29 Oct. 1977 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Marathon Oilers, 22 Nov. 1977 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian State, 26 Nov. 1977 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Georgia Southern, 28 Nov. 1977 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, Wake Forest, 2-3 Dec. 1977 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - NC State vs. Davidson, 7 Dec. 1977 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 10 Dec. 1977 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina, 17 Dec. 1977 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. St. Joseph's, 28 Dec. 1977 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duquesne, 29 Dec. 1977 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Biscayne, 4 Jan. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 7 Jan. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 11 Jan. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 14 Jan. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 18 Jan. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Iona, 21 Jan. 1978 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 25 Jan. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 28 Jan. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 31 Jan. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech, Furman (North-South Double Header), 3-4 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 11 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 15 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 18 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Notre Dame, 21 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 23 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 25 Feb. 1978 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament, 1-4 Mar. 1978 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - NIT Tournament (1 of 3), Mar. 1978 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - NIT Tournament (2 of 3), Mar. 1978 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - NIT Tournament (3 of 3), Mar. 1978 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Box scores, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1978-1979 (Legalbox 26, Folder 4)
  - General information, 1978-1979 (Legalbox 26, Folder 5)
  - Media guide, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1978-1979 (Legalbox 26, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Schedule, 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Score book, 1978-1979 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Score books, Mar. 1979 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, box scores, 1978-1979 (Legalbox 26, Folder 7)
  - Red-White game, 28 Oct. 1978 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Marathon Oilers, 20 Nov. 1978 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Big Four Tournament, 1-2 Dec. 1978 (Legalbox 26, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Davidson, 6 Dec. 1978 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Campbell, 9 Dec. 1978 (Legalbox 26, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Wilmington, 16 Dec. 1978 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Penn State, 29 Dec. 1978 (Legalbox 26, Folder 10)
  - NC State vs. Appalachian State, 2 Jan. 1979 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - NC State vs. Tulane, 5 Jan. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Long Beach State, 6 Jan. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 1)
  - NC State vs. Maryland, 10 Jan. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 13 Jan. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 2)
  - NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 17 Jan. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 21 Jan. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - NC State vs. East Carolina, 23 Jan. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Virginia, 27 Jan. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 30 Jan. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 5)
  - North-South Double Header program, 2-3 Feb. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - NC State vs. Virginia Tech (North-South Double Header), 2 Feb. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Furman (North-South Double Header), 3 Feb. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 6)
  - NC State vs. Notre Dame, 7 Feb. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 10 Feb. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Duke, 14 Feb. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - NC State vs. Clemson, 17 Feb. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - NC State vs. Wake Forest, 24 Feb. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - NCAA Tournament Eastern Regional program, 9-11 Mar. 1979 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Atlantic Coast Conference Tournament, 1-3 Mar. 1979 (Legalbox 27, Folder 10)
  - NCAA Tournament, East Regional (1 of 2), 9, 11 Mar. 1979 (Legalbox 28, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Tournament, East Regional (2 of 2), 9, 11 Mar. 1979 (Legalbox 28, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Legalbox 28, Folder 3)
  - General information, 1979-1980 (Legalbox 28, Folder 4)
  - Media guide, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball press releases, 1979-1980 (Legalbox 28, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Recruiting booklet, circa 1980s (Flatbox 271)
  - Score book, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Statistics, 1979-1980 (Legalbox 28, Folder 6)
  - Team photograph, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Ticket distribution policy, 1979-1980 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Red-White game, 10 Nov. 1979 (Box 85, Folder 5)